<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Created from PDF via Acrobat SaveAsXML -->
<!-- Mapping Table version: 13-Dec-2002 -->
<TaggedPDF-doc>
<x:xmpmeta xmlns:x='adobe:ns:meta/' x:xmptk='XMP toolkit 2.9.1-12, framework 1.6'>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf='http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#' xmlns:iX='http://ns.adobe.com/iX/1.0/'>
<rdf:Description rdf:about='uuid:e9ebc225-c58d-4e87-963b-4d8319220437' xmlns:pdf='http://ns.adobe.com/pdf/1.3/'></rdf:Description>
<rdf:Description rdf:about='uuid:e9ebc225-c58d-4e87-963b-4d8319220437' xmlns:xap='http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/' xap:ModifyDate='2003-01-08T13:55:59-08:00' xap:CreateDate='2003-01-08T13:55:59-08:00' xap:MetadataDate='2003-01-08T13:55:59-08:00'></rdf:Description>
<rdf:Description rdf:about='uuid:e9ebc225-c58d-4e87-963b-4d8319220437' xmlns:xapMM='http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/mm/' xapMM:DocumentID='uuid:70941ec3-e666-43a2-9dfa-eda347dbde48'/>
<rdf:Description rdf:about='uuid:e9ebc225-c58d-4e87-963b-4d8319220437' xmlns:dc='http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/' dc:format='application/pdf'/>
</rdf:RDF>
</x:xmpmeta>


<Part>
<H1>The Frogs Desiring a King
</H1>

<P>The Frogs were living as happy as could be in a marshy
swamp that just suited them. They went splashing
about, caring for nobody and nobody troubled them.
But some of the frogs thought that this was not right,
that they should have a king and a proper constitution,
so they sent up a petition to Zeus to give them what
they wanted.
“Mighty Zeus,” they cried, “send unto us a king that will
</P>

<P>rule over us and keep us in order.” Zeus laughed at their croaking and threw down into the swamp a huge Log. The </P>

<P>Frogs were frightened out of their lives by the commotion made in their midst, and all rushed to the bank to look at the </P>

<P>
<Link>continued . . . </Link>
</P>

<P>horrible monster. But after a time, seeing that it did not move, one or two of the boldest of them ventured out towards the Log, and even dared to touch it. Still it did not move. Then the greatest hero of the Frogs jumped upon the Log and commenced dancing up and down upon it; thereupon all the Frogs came and did the same, and for some time the Frogs went about their business every day without taking the slightest notice of their new King Log lying in their midst. But this did not suit them, so they sent another petition to Zeus, and said to him, “We want a real king; one that will really rule over us.” Now this made Zeus angry, so he sent them a big Stork that soon set to work gobbling them all up. Then the Frogs repented, but it was too late. </P>

<P>Better no rule than cruel rule. </P>
</Part>
</TaggedPDF-doc>
